Finding Aid for the Theodore Bikel Papers LSC.2321
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Correspondence and subject files, 1946-2012
  - Subseries 1.1: Chronological files, 1946-2002
    - AJC Governing Council, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Ambassador/ Peter Pan, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - American Shakespeare Th., 1976 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Auction requests, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - B general, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - B personal, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - B fan, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - J. Bernstein NY Office, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - J. Bernstein LAX Office, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Bikel, Josef & Miriam, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - C general, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - C personal, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - C fan, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Conference of Presidents of Major American Jewish Organiz., 1976 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Contracts fulfilled, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Contract correspondence dates completed, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Contracts tech. notes, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Frank Church, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - D general, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - D personal, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - D fan, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - E general, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - E personal, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Elektra Records, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - F general, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - F personal, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - F fan, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - G general, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - G personal, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - G fan, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Hartman Theatre - Stamford, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - H general, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - H personal, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - H fan, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - I general, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - I personal, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Inquiries plays, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Inquiries television, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Inquiries lectures, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Inquiries concerts, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - J general, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - J personal, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - J fan, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - JWB Music Council, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - JWB Lecture Bureau, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - K general, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - K personal, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - K fan, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - L personal, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - L fan, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - M general, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - M fan, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - M personal, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - William Morris general, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Wm. Morris completed, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Wm. Morris NY pending, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - National Endowment for the Arts - Theater Panel, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - North American Jewish Students Appeal, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - P general, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - P personal, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - P fan, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Pan Continental Tours, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Q personal, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - R general, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - R personal, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - R fan, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Charles Rapp Enterprises, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - S general, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - S personal, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - S fan, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - SAG, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - T general, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Wm. Takas, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Herb Tobias, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - U general, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - United Jewish Appeal, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Unsolicited music, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - V general, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - V personal, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - W general, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - W personal, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - W fan, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - World Jewish Film and Television Festival, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 3-4)
    - H. Walker Agency, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - XYZ general, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (letters sent), 1976 (Box 115, Folder 5-7)
    - A general, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - A personal, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - A fan, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - AJC Chapter Speaking, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - B general, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - B personal, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - B fan, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Jay Bernstein LAX office, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - C general, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - C personal, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - C fan, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Contract correspondence dates completed, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 3-4)
    - General correspondence (letters sent), 1977 (Box 116, Folder 5-6)
    - Contracts - tech. notes, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - D general, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - D personal, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - D fan, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - E general, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - E personal, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - E fan, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Elektra Records, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Eternal Light, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Expense reimbursement, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - F general, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - F personal, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - F fan, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Finkel, Elliott, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - "The Fifth Cup" - G. Kingsley, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - "Fifth Cup" Coachlight D.T., 1976 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - G general, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - G personal, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - G fan, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - H general, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - H personal, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - H fan, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Hartman Theatre - Stamford, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - I general, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - I personal, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - I fan, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Inauguration materials, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Israel, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Inquiries plays, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries lectures, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries television, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries films, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - J general, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - J fan, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - J personal, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Jewish Hall of Fame Honorary Advisory Board, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - JWB Lecture Bureau, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - JWB Jewish Music Council, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - K general, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - K fan, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - K personal, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - L general, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - L fan, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - L personal, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Lubavitch News Service, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - M general, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - M fan, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - M personal, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - McConnell, Kathleen, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Media project - Black-Jewish Info Center, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Wm. Morris NY pending, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Wm. Morris completed, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Wm. Morris general, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Wm. Morris LAX, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - N general, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - N fan, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - N personal, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Names various lists of names, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - National Academy of Television Arts & Sciences, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Assoc. Council of the Arts, 1978 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - AFL/CIO CPE, 1978 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - AEA - names & phone #s for officers, staff, 1978 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - AEA - Pay-TV Committee applications, 1978 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - AEA Pension/Welfare, 1978 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - AEA general, 1978 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - (AEA - loose), 1978 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - ACA (American Council for the Arts), 1978 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - B personal, 1978 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - C general, 1978 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Contracts - fulfilled, 1978 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (letters sent), 1978 (Box 119, Folder 6-7)
    - Inquiries television, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries plays, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries lectures, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries concert, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Israel, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - J general, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - J personal, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - J fan, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - JWB Jewish Music Council, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Jewish Theological Seminary "Eternal Light", 1978 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - K general, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - K fan, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - K personal, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - L general, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - L fan, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - L personal, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Lubavitch News Service, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - M general, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - M personal, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - National Arts Council correspondence re: appointment, 1978 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - (National Council for the Arts), 1978 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - NEA Ad Hoc Committee stars, 1978 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1978 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - National Endowment for the Arts Dance Panel, 1978 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - National Endowment for the Arts Theatre Panel, 1978 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - National Endowment for the Arts Folk Arts Panel, 1978 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - National Endowment for the Arts NASAA Policy & Planning Comm., 1978 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - National Endowment for the Arts grant applications/theatre, 1978 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - NEA grant applications, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - NEA - Reference Arts in Education - People, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - National Endowment Member/Directory & Biographies, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - National Foundation for Jewish Culture - Dr. Harry L. Barron, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - National Yiddish Theatre, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - New Directions, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Orders received, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - O general, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - P general, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - P personal, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - R general, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - R personal, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - R fan, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - S fan, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - S general, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - S personal, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - SAG, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Schedules, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Southern folklore, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Speaking research material, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Charles H. Stern, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - T general, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - T personal, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - T fan, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Wm. Takas, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Herb Tobias, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - U general, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - U fan, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - United Jewish Appeal, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Unsolicited music, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - V personal, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - W general, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - W personal, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - W fan, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - World Jewish Congress, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - XYZ general, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - XYZ personal, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Yiddish Films / YIVO, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Yiddish National Theatre, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - General A, 1979 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Personal A, 1979 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Academy of Motion Picture Arts & Sciences, 1979 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - The Artists Agency completed, 1979 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Autograph - photograph requests & fan mail, 1979-1981 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - (Personal B), 1979 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - General B, 1979 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Jay Bernstein - LAX office, 1979 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - (Bread and Roses), 1979 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Robin Berry, 1979 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - General C, 1979 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Personal C, 1979 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Cornish Institute Seattle 6/14, 1979 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Contracts fulfilled, 1979 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (letters sent), 1979 (Box 210, Folder 4-5)
    - Dates completed contract correspondence, 1979 (Box 124, Folder 3-6)
    - Personal D, 1979 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Drive Your Car Service, 1979 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Personal E, 1979 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - General E, 1979 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - General F, 1979 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Personal F, 1979 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Fan A - Z, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 1-2)
    - Jane Fonda, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Foster Parents Plan, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - General G, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Personal G, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - "Gershwin" - CBA, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Personal H, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Higher Than Heaven - UJA Taping Sept. 13, 14/ 79, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - General I, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Personal I, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Inquiries concert, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Inquiries good works, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Inquiries lectures, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Israel, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - General J, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Personal J, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Jewish calendar, 1978-1979 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - JWB Lecture Bureau, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - General K, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Personal K, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Killooleet - Hancock, Vermont, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Kramer and Reiss PR/West Coast, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - General L, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Personal L, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Lubavitch News Service, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - General M, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Personal M, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Manhattan Plaza East, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Media Project Black-Jewish Info. Center, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - The Mertz Company, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Wm. Morris general, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Wm. Morris completed, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Wm. Morris LAX, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Wm. Morris NY pending, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - General N, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Personal N, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Nat. Academy of Arts & Sciences, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Nat. Endowment for the Arts, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - NEA Policy & Planning, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - NEA Ballet West, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - NEA consultant, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - NEA travel vouchers, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - NEA Secretary of Defense, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - NEA Member/Directory & Biographies, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - NEA Council Challenge Review Comm., 1979 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - NEA theatre, 1979 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - NASAA general, 1979 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - (NEA & NEH files), 1979 (Box 127, Folder 2-4)
    - National Found. for Jew. Culture Dr. Harry L. Barron, 1979 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - National Public Radio Stravinsky taping 6/5/79, 1979 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - National Theatre - Washington D.C., 1979 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - New Canaan Country School, 1979 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - NYC apartment, 1979 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Office of Jewish Info., 1979 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Orders received, 1979 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - General O, 1979 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Personal O, 1979 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Perilla, Bob Associates PR/New York, 1979 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - General P, 1979 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Pan Continental Tours, 1979 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - General Q, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Personal Q, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Personal R, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - General R, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Vanessa Redgrave, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - General S, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Personal S, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Leo Shull, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Schedules, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - General T, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Personal T, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Ticket refund applic., 1979 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Temple Shearith Israel, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Theatre Communications Group, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Herb Tobias, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Wm. Takas, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - General U, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Personal U, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - General V, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Personal V, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - General W, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Personal W, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Warner Communications, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - General X, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Personal X, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - General Y, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Personal Y, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - General Z, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Personal Z, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Contracts fulfilled, 1967-1975 (Box 128, Folder 4-6, Box 129)
    - Programs concerts, 1962-1977 (Box 130, Folder 1-4)
    - Programs theatre, 1969-1970s (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Programs w/ orchestra, 1960s-1970s (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Urban affairs, 1960s-1970s (Box 131, Folder 1-2)
    - UNESCO, 1960s-1970s (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Vietnam, 1960s-1970s (Box 131, Folder 4-5)
    - Vietnam, 1960s-1970s (Box 132, Folder 1-2)
    - Violence, 1960s-1970s (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Welfare, 1960s-1970s (Box 132, Folder 4-5)
    - Women's rights, 1960s-1970s (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - World Jewish Congress, 1960s-1970s (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - WUJS (World Union of Jewish Students), 1960s-1970s (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Youth, 1960s-1970s (Box 133)
    - Youth, 1960s-1970s (Box 134, Folder 1-2)
    - Youth material, 1960s-1970s (Box 134, Folder 3-6)
    - Zionists, 1960s-1970s (Box 135, Folder 1-2)
    - AZYF (American Zionist Youth Foundation), 1960s-1970s (Box 135, Folder 3-4)
    - (American Zionist Youth Foundation Seminar for Campus Representatives), 1960s-1970s (Box 135, Folder 5-6)
    - Arena Stage Productions, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - General A, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Personal A, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Brel project - Sidlin, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - General C, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Personal C, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Celebrity auctions, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Contract corres. completed, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 3-4)
    - Contracts completed, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (letters sent), 1980 (Box 136, Folder 6, Box 137, Folder 1)
    - General D, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Personal D, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - General E, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Personal E, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - General F, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Personal F, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - "Fiddler" Stratford, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - General G, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Personal G, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - General H, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Personal H, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - General I, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Personal I, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Rivka Isachar, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Inquiries movies & TV, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Inquiries concerts, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Inquiries good works, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Personal J, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - General J, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - JWB Jewish Music Council, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Personal K, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - General K, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Personal L, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - General L, 1980 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Personal M, 1980 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - General M, 1980 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Manhattan Plaza, 1980 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Greg Mullins corres., 1980 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Wm. Morris gen'l corres., 1980 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Personal N, 1980 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - General N, 1980 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Ed Robbins corres., 1980 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Personal T, 1980 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - UJA 1979 contribution, 1980 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - (Washington Speaker's Bureau?), 1980 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - (Actors' Equity Association), 1981 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - AJC Executive Committee, 1981 (Box 138, Folder 5-6)
    - The Arts Edge Conference Oct. 81, 1981 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Autograph requests/ fan mail, 1981 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Bob Hope Anta Award The Denver Post, 1981 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Celebrity auctions, 1981 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Contract correspondence completed May-June, 1981 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - (Contract correspondence), 1981 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - (Contract correspondence - loose), 1981 (Box 139, Folder 3-4)
    - Correspondence Jan/June (letters sent), 1981 (Box 139, Folder 5-6)
    - Correspondence Jul/Dec (letters sent), 1981 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - General E, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - General F, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Film Artists & Associates Dick Heckenkamp, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - General G, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Holiday gifts, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Inquiries good works, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Inquiries theatre, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Inquiries interviews etc., 1981 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Inquiries concerts + lectures + symphony, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Invitations, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Personal J, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - General J, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - (J), 1981 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - General K, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Personal K, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Kramer & Reiss, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - General L, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - General M, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Personal M, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - William Morris Agency general correspondence, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Greg Mullins correspondence, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - General N, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - NEA general correspondence, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - NEA material, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - NEA expense reimb., 1981 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - NEA Bikel proposals, 1978-1981 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - National Foundation for Jewish Culture, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Orders placed, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Orders received, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - General O, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - General P, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Pan Continental Tours, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Personal R, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Ed Robbins correspondence, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - General S, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - (Schedules?), 1981 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Star Island Conference, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - (T?), 1981 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - General T, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - (Takas), 1981 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Task Force August 1981/LA (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Task Force 8/81, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Task Force 8/81, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - ULLICO correspondence & completed claim forms to Equity, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - General V, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - (W), 1981 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - General W, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - (Z), 1981 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Actors Fund/ Night of 100 Stars, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - AEA correspondence, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - AEA expense reimbursement, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - AJC general, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 4)